I'm really sorry.
Does he wear glasses
or contact lenses?
Glasses.
You'll have to hurry up.
He decided that his brown leather shoes
were the best pair to wear.
His back hurt a little
but not like other times in the past...
...when the pain was intolerable.
He was thinking his wife
didn't love him at all anymore.
He didn't burst into tears...
...and he didn't think
that the first thing most people do...
...when they realise someone
doesn't love them anymore is cry.
Sir, do you mind taking a look
into the camera here for me?
That will do. Thank you.
Have you ever been
on your own before?
No, never.
- Are you allergic to any foods?
- No.
Your last relationship
lasted how many years?
Around 12.
- Do you remember how long exactly, sir?
- Eleven years and one month.
- Sexual preference?
- Women.
However, I had one homosexual
experience in the past. In college.
Is there a bisexual option available?
No, sir, this option is no longer available
since about last summer...
...due to several operational problems.
I'm afraid you have to decide right now...
...if you want to be registered
as a homosexual or a heterosexual.
I think I should be registered
as a heterosexual.
- Any children, sir?
- No.
And the dog?
My brother. He was here years ago,
but he didn't make it.
You might remember him.
Medium build, 48 years old,
bald patch, blond hair.
I'm afraid not, sir.
Okay, I would like you to write
your name clearly on this form.
In capital letters. And sign it, please.
That will do. Thank you very much.
Okay, so you are not allowed to use
the volleyball or the tennis courts.
These are only for the couples.
You can use the facilities
for individual sports...
...such as squash and golf.
You can stay in the hotel
for up to 45 days.
You'll stay in a single room.
If everything goes well,
you'll be moved to a double room.
Come on, Bob.
I'm afraid you cannot keep
any of your personal belongings.
We will provide everything you need
as far as garments...
...accessories and shoes
are concerned.
- You can keep this.
- Thank you.
- Shoe size, please?
- Forty-four and a half.
Forty-four or 45?
There are no half sizes.
Forty-five.
If you need a haircut,
call reception one day ahead.
Smoking is not allowed.
You'll be able to run longer
during the hunt without getting tired...
...and your breath won't smell
when you kiss.
Enjoy your stay.
Excuse me.
If we need to get a haircut...
...we must call the reception
the day before?
- That's right.
- Great.
His room number was 101.
A tranquillizer gun was hanging
on the wall above his bed.
On the table
were 20 tranquilizer darts...
...a black plastic watch...
...a pair of sunglasses
and a cologne for men.
Inside the wardrobe
were four identical grey trousers...
...four identical button down shirts
in white and blue...
...a belt, socks, underwear, a blazer...
...a striped tie and a white bathrobe.
He looked out the window.
The unconscious bodies
of the captured loners...
...were lying on the wet ground.
"Thank God they wear
those waterproof ponchos," he thought.
Room 195. Two loners, two extra days.
Room 272. One loner, one extra day.
Hello. I'm the hotel manager
and this gentleman is my partner.
We'd like to welcome you.
You're one of the lucky ones.
You have one of our superior rooms,
which means you have a view.
Did you read the leaflet?
- Yes, I did.
- Very good.
The fact that you'll turn into an animal
if you fail to fall in love with someone...
...is not something
that should upset you, or get you down.
Just think, as an animal you'll have
a second chance to find a companion.
But even then you must be careful.
You need to choose a companion
that is a similar type of animal to you.
A wolf and a penguin
could never live together.
Nor could a camel and a hippopotamus.
That would be absurd. Think about it.
I understand this discussion
is a little unpleasant for you.
But it is my duty to prepare you,
psychologically...
...for all possible outcomes.
Have you thought of
what animal you'd like to be?
- Yes. A lobster.
- Why a lobster?
Because lobsters live
for over 100 years...
...are blue-blooded like aristocrats...
...and stay fertile all their lives.
I also like the sea very much.
I water-ski and swim quite well,
since I was a teenager.
I must congratulate you.
The first thing most people think of
is a dog.
Which is why the world is full of dogs.
Few people choose an unusual animal...
...which is why they are endangered.
A lobster is an excellent choice.
Could you stand for us, please?
This is to show you how easy life is...
...when there are two of something
rather than just one.
We tend to forget that
from time to time.
The handcuff will be removed
at the same time tomorrow.
- Sorry, Bob.
- Hope you enjoy your stay with us.
Goodbye.
Have a good day.
Good morning. Room 101.
Forty-four days left.
Breakfast is served.
Sit where you like.
His first day
was one he'd never forget.
Near his table at breakfast...
...sat a young woman
with her head tilted back.
Later he would learn
that she often got nosebleeds.
Next to her sat her best friend.
He thanked the waiter
who served him his coffee...
...and thought about his wife
for a moment.
A woman who seemed to like
butter biscuits...
...offered one to a man...
...drinking a Campari and soda
for breakfast.
He then looked behind him
and saw a woman...
...who he would later find out
was absolutely heartless.
And some others
in the couples area...
...whom he'd never meet
during his stay at the hotel.
That morning he was really hungry.
He could have eaten a whole chicken,
but ate almost nothing.
- Hello.
I decided to go for a walk
with my new friend.
Let me introduce you. This is Robert.
He stays in the room next to mine
and has a lisp.
Pleased to meet you.
I'm staying in Room 101.
I'm on the same floor. I'm 186.
- Would you like to join us?
- Why not?
One of these days
it's gonna be me on those yachts.
What are those yachts?
The final ordeal before letting you go,
and the hardest one.
Fifteen days of vacation,
just a couple, alone.
- Didn't you read the leaflet?
- I did.
- Have you seen John's leg?
- No.
John, would you show your leg?
Oh, yeah.
Room 187, Day 2.
Hello, everyone.
My mother was left on her own
when my father fell in love...
...with a woman
who was better at math than she was.
She had a postgraduate degree, I think,
whereas my mother was only a graduate.
I was 19 at the time.
My mother entered the hotel...
...but didn't make it
and was turned into a wolf.
I really missed her.
I found out she'd been moved to a zoo.
I often went there to see her.
I'd give her raw meat.
I knew wolves liked raw meat...
...but I couldn't figure out
which was my mother...
...so I used to give a little bit
to each of them.
One day I decided
to enter the enclosure.
I really missed her and I wanted a hug.
I climbed the fence and jumped in.
All the wolves charged at once
and attacked me.
All but two, who stood motionless.
My guess is that one of those two
must have been my mother.
The zoo guards got to me quite quickly
and took me to the hospital.
Thankfully, I didn't lose my leg,
I just have this limp...
...which is also
my defining characteristic.
My wife died six days ago.
She was very beautiful
and I loved her very much.
She had a limp too.
Thank you, John.
You can return to your seat now.
Let's move on to our next guest.
Room 104, Day 2.
Hello, everyone.
This is only my second day here...
...but already I feel like a member
of a wonderful group.
My defining characteristic
is that I have a very beautiful smile.
- Have you ever danced with anybody?
- Sorry?
- Yes.
What sort of dancing did you do?
Just depends on the music.
- Do you need to sit down?
- No, no, no, I'm getting ready to dance.
Can I sit here?
Sorry.
- Can I sit here?
- Of course.
Let me introduce you
to my best friend.
That woman you were talking to
has no feelings whatsoever.
She feels nothing at all.
She's the best hunter in the hotel.
Silent and very fast.
She's the women's record holder.
A hundred and ninety-two captives.
Would you like to dance?
I'm sorry,
I've got blood on your shirt.
Don't worry, there are many ways
to remove blood stains.
One way is to rinse clothes
with cold water, then rub with sea salt.
Another is to scrub with cotton wool
dipped in ammonia.
The third way is to mix
flour and water into a paste...
...especially if the clothes
are delicate or brightly coloured.
But just never use
warm water on blood. Ever.
Okay.
I think I have to rest for a little bit.
My leg's hurting.
That's okay.
Well, let me know when you feel better
and we can dance again.
Leave the room in an orderly fashion.
Do hurry up, but please be careful.
Nobody needs to get hurt or injured.
And good luck with the hunt.
I wish I didn't have this limp.
I used to be very good at running,
but not anymore.
I'm sure I'll be slower than them.
If I were you, I'd think of some tricks
that use the element of surprise...
...instead of speed.
You're right.
That's what I'll do.
Room 186. One loner, one extra day.
Thirty-eight days' stay left, plus 1,39.
Room 180.
The days of your stay
remain unchanged.
Room 290.
Four loners, four extra days.
One hundred and fifty-four days left,
plus 4,158.
Room 101.
The days of your stay remain unchanged.
Thirty-two days left.
Breakfast is served.
Man eats alone.
- How many darts did you use yesterday?
- Twelve.
Please take off your trousers
and sit on the bed.
Can we not do this today? It's awful.
I know.
But I'm afraid we have to do it.
And you have no idea
how much it helps psychologically...
...in your search for a partner.
Man eats with woman.
Lie down.
Spread your legs. More.
- Is your room number 186?
- Yes, it is.
You know masturbation
is not permitted in the rooms...
- ...or any other area of the hotel.
- Yes.
And yet it has been
brought to my attention...
...that you continue to do it.
Today you became erect quicker
than on other days. That's good.
- Please, just a little longer.
- Have a good day.
That's awful. Just awful.
Were you looking at a photo
while masturbating?
Yes.
What did the photograph show?
A naked woman on a horse
in the country.
If I were in your shoes...
...I would not be ogling the naked woman
but the horse.
I'm sure that horse was once a weak
and cowardly man just like you.
Woman walks alone.
Help.
Help. Help.
This is not necessary.
Please, it was an accident.
I just got carried away.
This is not necessary.
- Place your hand in the toaster.
- This could be a warning.
Look, I've been good otherwise. I...
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! Please!
Please, please, I'm sorry!
Woman walks with man.
What they do
as soon as you enter the room...
...is wash your body and your head
really well.
How do you know?
My uncle used to know a waiter
who worked here.
No waiters know about the procedure.
They're not allowed inside that room.
Nevertheless, they peel off the skin...
...which has become soft
due to the water and soap.
Afterwards they remove
the heart, the eyes...
...and other vital organs of the body
with a laser or scalpels.
Then the procedure changes according
to the animal one has chosen.
That makes total sense.
I mean, I suppose mammals
demand a different kind of work than...
- ...fowls, for example.
- Exactly.
After,
they throw the remaining body parts...
...in casks
outside the hotel's restaurant...
...and distribute the blood
to the hospitals in the city.
Why is that?
The blood is used for surgeries...
...where there are no blood donors
available.
- New guests arrived yesterday.
- Yes, I saw.
- I think I saw a woman with a limp.
- It's just a sprained ankle.
- She'll walk normally in a few days.
- That's a shame.
That is a shame, indeed.
One night on the coach...
...he sat next to the woman
who liked butter biscuits.
He gazed out of the window,
not looking at anything in particular...
...just trying to avoid talking to her.
- How's Bob?
- He's fine.
I'd give anything to go for a walk
with you and Bob one afternoon.
The dog's not allowed out of the room,
I'm afraid.
"There are some excuses
that no one can argue with," he thought.
Some excuses are, without doubt,
better than others.
And that was a really good one.
These biscuits are for Bob.
I want you to give them to him
whenever you want to reward him.
- Tell him they're from me.
- Thank you.
Can I come to your room sometime
for a chat?
I could give you a blow job,
or you can just fuck me.
I always swallow after fellatio...
...and I've got no problem with anal sex
if that's your thing.
My ex-husband always said...
...I had the most beautiful thighs
he'd ever seen...
...but let's not talk about him.
My room number is 180.
So my telephone extension is 180.
I hope I catch some loners tonight.
I haven't caught any the last few nights.
- Hope you catch lots too.
- Thank you very much.
If I don't find
a suitable partner soon...
...I'm gonna kill myself by
throwing myself out of one of the rooms.
Out of the window.
I want you to know that.
My room is on the first floor.
"I hope I catch some loners today,"
she said.
"And I hope you catch lots too."
She then told him...
...that if she didn't find
a suitable partner soon...
...she was going to kill herself...
...by jumping
from one of the room windows.
Three-twenty, maybe.
Or one higher up, 480,
that would be even better.
When she stopped talking,
he stared at her blankly...
...not knowing what to say.
He then looked out at the woods...
...and thought once more
how good his excuse had been.
Not bad. Bit higher.
Pull it back.
Have you thought about what animals
you wanna be if you don't make it?
A lobster.
I'm gonna be a parrot
if I don't make it.
Why don't you become parrots too?
And then we'll all be together.
You're a complete idiot. Picking one
of the few animals that can talk...
...when you have a speech impediment.
You'll lisp, even as an animal.
As for you, they'll catch you and put you
in a pot of boiling water until you die.
Then they'll crack open your claws
with pliers...
...and suck out your flesh
with their mouths.
You're pathetic, both of you.
I'm not gonna be turned
into some animal.
I'll come and visit you, though,
with my partner...
...when we're walking in some park
or when we're swimming in the sea...
...or when we're on one of our trips.
Friends.
Room 187, please.
It's no coincidence that the targets
are shaped like single people...
...and not couples.
- Hello.
- Your swimsuit is very nice.
- Thank...
- Thank you very much.
- You're welcome.
Do you like to swim breaststroke,
front crawl, butterfly or backstroke?
I like all strokes equally.
You know, I love breaststroke. No, really.
My friends often tease me and say:
"Stop swimming breaststroke
all the time."
And then they laugh.
Breaststroke is great.
It's excellent exercise for the back.
When swimming breaststroke...
...men shouldn't wear swim shorts...
...as it really limits movement
in the buttocks.
But you knew that, didn't you?
- I think your nose is bleeding.
- Really?
Oh, no.
This happens to me all the time.
It's really, really annoying.
I know.
I have a nosebleed problem too.
I saw what you did. It must have hurt.
Is it coming out?
No.
Yes.
- Can I use a tissue?
- Yes.
I'm gonna ask you a question
and I want you to answer me honestly.
What's worse,
to die of cold and hunger in the woods...
...to become an animal that will be killed
and eaten by some bigger animal...
...or to have a nosebleed
from time to time?
To become an animal
that will be killed by a bigger animal.
Exactly.
- She doesn't suspect that you're lying?
- No.
I'm very happy
because we have a new couple.
They met just two days ago...
...but they are very much in love,
and perfectly suited.
They both have the same problem
with their noses.
They bleed quite suddenly.
They'll be transferred
to a double room...
...with a larger wardrobe
and a larger bathroom.
They will remain there
for two weeks...
...and then be transferred to the yachts
for a further two weeks.
We wish you every success...
...and we hope
you will return to the city as a couple.
- I'm very happy.
- Me too.
Congratulations.
The course of your relationship
will be monitored closely...
...by our staff, and by me personally.
If you encounter any problems,
tensions, any arguing...
...that you cannot resolve,
you will be assigned children.
That usually helps. A lot.
Good morning. Room 101.
Seven days left. Breakfast is served.
You have really nice hair.
I know. Look.
How do you like mine?
Well, I think you have quite dry hair.
The colour is okay, though.
The most important thing
is that you're not bald.
However, when it comes to men...
...baldness is always a possibility
you can't avoid.
- Is your father bald?
- No, he isn't.
And even if I lose my hair...
...there are things I can do to get it back.
I can have a hair transplant.
- You can tell when someone's had one.
- I know.
Nice hair is not something you can get.
It's something you're born with.
And the fact that your father isn't bald
shouldn't put you at ease.
Have you decided what
you're going to do on your last day?
I'm still thinking about it.
Morning, ladies.
So today is your last day...
...and as is customary, you can choose
how to spend your last night.
What I always say
in these situations...
...is it'd be wise to choose something
you can't do as an animal.
For example,
read a work of classic literature...
...or sing a song you really like.
It would be silly to choose,
for example...
...a walk in the grounds...
...or to have sexual intercourse
with another person...
...because those are things
you can do as an animal.
First, your best friend has written
something she'd like to read to you...
...which is really very touching.
"We always sat together at school...
...and whenever I had a problem
I'd talk to you about it...
...because you always
gave the best advice.
When we didn't manage to find
dance partners at the prom...
...the fact that we were together at
that difficult moment gave me strength.
I'm sorry
that things have come to this.
I'm sure if you had a few more days,
you would find someone just like I did...
...because you're an admirable person
with beautiful hair and very nice breasts.
I was always jealous of your hair,
you know that.
You were, are, and always will be my
best friend, and I'll think of you often...
...and I'll always wear
those silver earrings...
...you gave me for my birthday.
I'll miss you.
And however many new girlfriends
I make in a few days...
...when I move back into the city,
I don't think I'll find another as true..."
I'd like to watch Stand by Me...
...with River Phoenix, Kiefer Sutherland
and Richard Dreyfuss. Alone.
Excellent choice. Lovely film.
Please leave a message.
Hello. You're probably
in the bathroom...
...and that's why
you can't hear the phone.
Nothing like a cold shower
in the morning.
Well, I'll call you a little bit later.
After you've finished your shower.
We'll talk later. Bye.
One day, as he was playing golf,
he thought that it is more difficult...
...to pretend that you do have feelings
when you don't...
...than to pretend
you don't have feelings when you do.
He also thought
that he liked her accent...
...and he'd always preferred women
with short hair.
So he decided that she was the one.
During the hunt, he would follow her...
...and as soon as she shot a loner
he would say to her:
"I wish we had real guns
instead of these silly tranquillizer ones.
Why don't you kill him
with your bare hands?"
And the moment she put her hands
around the loner's throat...
...he would say,
"I hope he dies right away."
What happened?
She jumped from the window
of Room 180.
- There's blood and biscuits everywhere.
- I hope she dies right away.
On second thought...
...I hope she suffers quite a bit
before she dies.
I just hope her pathetic screams
can't be heard from my room...
...because I was thinking about having
a lie down, and I need peace and quiet.
I was playing golf
and I'm quite tired.
The last thing I need is some woman
dying slowly and loudly.
I can't hear you
with all the screaming.
We'll talk some other time
when it's quieter.
Goodbye.
One message.
Hello. You're probably
in the bathroom...
...and that's why you can't hear
the phone.
Nothing like a cold shower
in the morning.
Well, I'll call you a little bit later.
After you've finished your shower.
We'll talk later. Bye.
Mind if I join you?
A martini.
- I think we are a match.
- Yes, I think so too.
The keys to the double room, please.
I wish you the best of luck.
We all wish you the best of luck.
Do you sleep on the left side of the bed
or the right?
- The right. You?
- The left. Perfect.
Spread your legs.
Should I turn off the light
or would you like to read?
I'd like to read.
Does the light bother you?
No. I'm not bothered
by light or noise.
I'm a deep sleeper.
- Hello.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
This is our new daughter.
Her name's Elizabeth.
Elizabeth, give the nice man a kiss.
He's a friend of mine.
The last thing I want right now
is a kiss from a silly little girl.
Come on, move away.
Don't cry, Elizabeth,
you should thank me.
Now you'll have a limp
and be more like your father.
What was that sound?
Did you say something?
No.
You mind if we fuck in a position
where I can see your face?
Sure.
Turn the light on, please,
so I can see you better.
Good morning.
Morning.
I killed your brother.
I left him to die very slowly.
He may not be dead yet,
even as we speak.
I was kicking him for ages.
It doesn't matter.
He whined a little.
A strange kind of bark.
Something like this:
It must have been from the pain.
- You didn't hear anything?
- No.
You really are a deep sleeper.
- Would you like some coffee?
- I'd love some.
As soon as I wash my face
and brush my teeth, though.
I can't wait to hear the story
you promised to tell me last night...
...about that student of yours
at the university...
...and his awful final project.
It's really a very funny story.
His name was Ryess.
R-Y-E-S-S. Ryess.
These aren't tears. It's just water.
I just washed my face.
I knew you were lying.
I can't understand why you did it
when you know well...
...a relationship cannot be built on a lie.
We're going to the hotel manager now.
- You'll get the punishment you deserve.
- What's the punishment for this?
They turn you into the animal
no one wants to be.
I saw your partner
running back that way.
He looked frantic.
Is everything okay?
At first he wanted to kill her
in some horrible and painful way...
...like the death she had inflicted
on his brother.
He thought about kicking her
in the stomach over and over again...
...and then stabbing her
in the same spot, in the stomach.
But then he thought
there wouldn't be much point...
...because she was already
unconscious...
...and wouldn't feel any pain
from the kicks or the knife.
You have to shoot me
so they won't suspect I helped you.
A hotel maid helped him.
He couldn't understand why she did it.
So he decided to turn her
into an animal.
He dragged her to the room
where the transformations took place.
I asked him many times
what sort of animal he turned her into...
...but he always gave me
the same answer:
"That's none of your concern."
That night he left the hotel,
once and for all.
He began to run
without knowing where he was headed.
But he was headed towards us.
This was the start of his new life.
And back then he didn't know
how much it hurts to be alone...
...how much it hurts
when you can't reach...
...to rub pain relief ointment
on your back...
...and you are constantly in pain.
I found him in the woods.
He escaped from the hotel.
- Are you a doctor, by any chance?
- No.
That's a pity.
We need a doctor around.
We had one but they caught him
a couple months ago.
I'm an architect.
That's okay. So welcome.
You can stay with us
for as long as you like.
You can be a loner until the day you die,
there is no time limit.
Thank you very much.
By the way...
...any romantic or sexual relations
between loners are not permitted.
And any such acts are punished.
Is that clear?
Can I have a conversation
with someone?
Of course you can...
...so long as there is no flirting
or anything like that.
That applies to dance nights as well.
We all dance by ourselves, that's why
we only play electronic music.
What happened to your mouth?
He can't speak.
He was given the Red Kiss.
- What's the Red Kiss?
- We slashed his lips with a razor...
...and the lips of another loner
and we forced them to kiss.
That was a couple of days ago now...
...but the cuts were deep,
and they're still in pain.
They were flirting, you know?
Some punishments
are worse than other punishments.
Having your thumb cut is worse
than having your head shaved.
And having a hot-boiled egg
under your armpit...
...is worse than having
your leg kicked.
The punishment I'm afraid of
isn't the Red Kiss...
...but another one
that is called the Red Intercourse.
I have never seen it happen...
...but it's not difficult to imagine
what it means.
Oh, my God, I am so afraid of it.
Move!
Hide!
That was the first time I saw him.
He was hiding behind a tree
close to mine.
He seemed quite presentable.
The next day, in the city,
he found out that I was shortsighted too.
Hide!
That night, in my sleep...
...I dreamt that we lived
in a big house together in the city...
...with a large, well-lit kitchen.
And I was wearing dark blue trousers
and a tight green blouse.
And he took my clothes off
and fucked me up the ass.
And as he was fucking me,
a thug came into the kitchen...
...and took the steak knives
from the drawer...
...and attacked us, stabbing the knives
into our bellies, one by one.
I woke up terrified.
Try harder. Don't give up.
You know you should've been
more careful.
Try harder or they'll find you
and you'll be turned into an animal.
A weak one.
We must get a move on now.
It's too dangerous to stay here.
If you manage to free yourself,
run as fast as you can and find us.
If you free yourself
but think you'll die from the bleeding...
...go straight to your grave.
- Have you dug your own grave?
- Yes.
Very good. That's enough for now.
I'm going to go hunting for truffles.
They are delicious and quite rare.
- A kilo can fetch a lot of money.
- You'll need a pig.
- Impossible to find otherwise.
- I know.
Don't be long.
Gotta get back in 50 minutes.
Okay.
- Hello, David.
- Hello, Robert.
What you did to that woman
was dreadful.
She killed my brother.
I'd do the same thing
if she'd killed you.
You're like a brother to me.
My best friend in the whole world.
I don't think I'm your best friend
in the whole world.
- You used to spend more time with John.
- Who's John?
- John, the Limping Man.
- Oh, yeah.
I didn't even remember his name.
Or his face.
You're the one I think of
whenever I need a friend.
Nevertheless, did John make it?
They're getting ready for the yacht.
It all begins this week.
Everyone says they're gonna make it.
They're perfectly suited and the child
will help them get past the fighting.
- That's great.
- You're not thinking about coming back?
If you told the hotel manager
about your brother she'd forgive you.
No. It's really nice to be on your own.
There's no one tying you down.
You listen to music whenever you like...
...you masturbate whenever you want,
go for walks whenever you like...
...have a chat whenever you like.
I don't miss companionship at all.
I just miss you
because you were my one true friend.
- Are you gonna shoot me?
- I'm afraid so.
- I only have two days left.
- What did you say?
I can't understand
the way you speak.
I'm going to shoot you.
I only have two days left.
I need more time.
You believe
another day will make a difference?
Have you seen how ugly you are?
You haven't got a chance.
If I was a woman, I...
Don't tell anyone I helped you.
If you want to repay me, there is a way,
if you kill a rabbit, bring it to me to eat.
- Do you promise?
- Yes.
- Bye.
- Hello.
- Did you bring the stuff I asked for?
- Of course.
The gun is in the folder, as are the keys
and the numbers of the double rooms.
Try not to lose the key cards. I have
to return them to where I found them.
I suggest tomorrow, Saturday, because
after the dance, everyone will be tired.
And many of the staff
are off work at the weekend.
What about the shampoo?
I forgot it.
I'll bring you two bottles next time.
You're terrific, do you know that?
Please make a note of the shampoo
so you don't forget it.
I have to tell you something.
What is it?
This will be my last mission.
I can't take it anymore.
I can't live in that horrible house
with that fat dentist.
He's always asking
whether I've flossed.
And forces me to brush my teeth
after every meal, however small.
When we are done with the big night
we've got planned...
...you can come and live with us
and I'll find another insider.
I doubt I'll find anyone
as efficient as you are.
But I must respect your wishes.
Just be patient for a few more days...
...and don't forget to take your
birth control pills, okay?
Thank you.
No, we thank you.
You are brilliant.
You carefully flay the rabbit
with a sharp knife and cut off its head.
You then slice open its belly...
...and stuff it with well-washed
red and green peppers.
Not too spicy,
and a little garlic and mint.
You then soak it in lemon juice...
...and leave it a while
to marinate the flesh...
...before you skewer it on a stick...
...and roast it over the fire
for about an hour.
That's my favourite food. Rabbit.
Woman. Brunette. Fifty years old.
Marriage certificate expired
two months ago.
- My husband's away on a business trip.
- Yeah. Okay. Can I have a look?
Hands.
No dirt under her nails
or mud on her shoes.
9 Belsize Road.
- So your husband is away?
- Yes.
- Where?
- Bath.
Good morning, sir.
Are you here alone?
Good morning, officer.
No, I'm here with my partner.
She's inside one of the stores,
shopping, right now.
Can I see your certificate, please?
My partner keeps it in her purse.
You see, I am losing it all the time.
I see.
And what store is she shopping in?
Oh, here she is.
I'm sorry, darling.
They had such a huge variety
of pain relief ointment.
I bought you this.
I hope it's what you were looking for.
That's wonderful, dear.
Can I have my certificate, please?
Of course, darling.
Would you like to see mine also,
officer?
No, that's okay.
Thank you, sir. You have a good day.
Thank you, officer.
You have a good day.
- Madam.
- Sir.
If I'm walking too slowly just say,
and I'll pick up my pace.
This pace is fine.
Maybe don't squeeze my hand so tightly,
my palm's getting a little sweaty.
- Better?
- Yes, much better.
Are you planning on buying
anything else nice while we're here?
Yes, contact lens solution
and a Parker Rollerball.
I didn't know you were shortsighted.
I'm shortsighted too.
Will you stay a few days?
I'm afraid not, Papa.
We're heading back again today.
Tomorrow I'm going away
on a business trip.
You know how demanding my job is.
Don't ask if I can stay a few days
every time I come.
Do you all work
for the same company?
- Yes.
My daughter says to me
it's a very fine company.
Do you agree?
- It's a rather good company.
- It is.
One of the best, I'd say.
The only problem with the job...
...is that I don't have enough time
for my wife and kids.
- We have four beautiful children.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
But even if we'd never had children,
I would never dream of leaving my wife.
Even if it was just the two of us,
on our own, we'd go on trips.
We'd go to Portofino in Italy...
...or go to a Greek island
for the summer...
...and so our relationship would be
as intense as it was at the start.
I love my wife so much
I could die for her.
That's how much I love her.
For your first day in the city,
you did great.
That part about holiday destinations
in the Mediterranean was brilliant.
Thank you very much.
When did you become shortsighted?
When I was 16.
- You?
- When I was 12.
What was the make of your
first pair of glasses?
I don't remember.
- Do you have astigmatism too?
- Yes.
Would you like me to rub
some balm on your back...
...on the bits
you can't reach on your own?
I'd like that.
- Here?
- A little lower, please.
- Yes.
"Hello, everyone, and good luck.
The room numbers are as follows.
Room 306, the hotel manager
and her partner.
They both have nice voices.
Room 240, couple who both love to ski.
Room 282, couple who both
studied social sciences.
Name of yacht, Bliss,
couple prone to nosebleeds."
You and you take 306.
You and you take 240.
You take 282.
- And you two, take the yacht.
- Can I go to the yacht?
Okay, then. So you take the yacht.
And you take 282.
And us three,
we'll take the manager's room.
We have 40 minutes.
You need to speak with the manager.
Wake up. Get up.
Sit in that seat over there.
Put your hand behind your back.
A basketball weighs
between 550 and 650 grams.
- Did you know that?
- No, I didn't know that.
Yes.
The weight's different
for men's and women's games...
...but that's roughly
how much it weighs.
Do you know how much
a volleyball weighs?
- No, but I'd like to find out.
- Good evening.
- I have something to tell you.
His nose
doesn't really bleed on its own.
He bangs it against a wall or a piece
of hardwood or something like that.
Or he cuts it with a penknife when you're
not looking. You two are not suited.
Shut up.
Dad, tell him to leave. I'm sleepy.
And I'm quite sure
that stain on his T-shirt isn't blood...
...but cherry juice or ketchup
or red watercolor paint...
...or something like that.
Or beetroot juice.
Do you love her?
With all my heart.
How much do you love her,
on a scale of 1 to 15?
Fourteen.
Fourteen is a very impressive score.
He loves her very much indeed.
Who do you think we should kill?
Who will be able
to live on their own better?
Here's a knife, Mum. Kill him.
- You'd better get out while you still can.
- Okay.
That's all I came to say anyway.
You, if this woman dies, do you think
you'll manage on your own...
...or will you be with someone else?
No. I can live alone, she can't.
I'm on my own for hours
when she's running the hotel.
I like sitting in the room.
It relaxes me, calms me.
I like it a lot.
I can definitely live on my own.
- No!
- Be quiet.
Take it.
Shoot her.
No! No!
No! Oh, my God, no!
Where were you?
I was looking for you.
I was masturbating
behind those trees over there.
- Why aren't you dancing?
- My leg is a little sore.
- Did you dig your grave?
- Not yet.
I don't mean to pressure you...
...or to ruin the mood
now that we're celebrating...
...but at some point
you'll have to do it.
Don't expect anyone else
to dig your grave for you...
...or to carry your corpse.
We'll throw some dirt over you,
but that's about it.
Tomorrow, find a spot you like...
...where the ground isn't too rocky,
and make a start.
- Enjoy the rest of your evening.
- Thank you.
As soon as his last patient left
I entered his office and I said to him:
"Honey, the dinner is ready.
But, I'm not sure I can eat right now.
One of my front teeth hurts a lot.
Can you take a look, please, dear?"
"Yes, sure, no problem," he said.
And the minute he turned his head...
...I took the drill,
and I shoved it into his chest.
That story sounds really interesting,
but I have to leave.
I just remembered
I left batteries next to a tree.
And the last thing I want
is to lose them. Sorry.
- Did you catch rabbits?
- No, someone brought me them.
- Who?
- A friend of mine.
- Do you want one?
- No.
You don't need to accept rabbits
from others.
If you need more rabbits,
just ask and I'll bring you more.
Catching a rabbit is difficult,
but I'll try.
There's no need for you
to be indebted to the others.
Thank you very much.
The man who brought you the rabbits,
is he shortsighted?
I don't know. I don't think so.
Okay.
Is that a sparrow up in that tree?
I can't really see that far,
but I don't think so.
- Are you shortsighted?
- No.
- You're lying.
- It's the truth.
What does it say here?
"YKK."
You knew that already.
All zips say the same thing.
I'm not shortsighted.
I don't understand
why you won't believe me.
I can see really clearly.
I used to be a pilot.
You're wearing contact lenses.
I don't wear contact lenses.
I'm not shortsighted. I swear.
You are.
You think I'm an idiot and can't tell.
Let me see.
I wanna see your eyes.
Look up. Look up!
Up, up.
Look down now.
Look left.
Look right. Up again.
I'm sorry.
I thought you were trying to fool me.
For this synchronization exercise
we have to fully concentrate...
...as we both have to press play
at exactly the same time.
- Why don't we just use one headset?
- Because that's the whole point.
This is an exercise for us.
- We have to be totally synchronized.
- Okay.
- I'm ready.
Five, four, three, two...
We've developed a code...
...so we can communicate
with each other...
...even in front of the others...
...without them knowing
what we are saying.
When we turn our heads to the left
it means:
"I love you more
than anything in the world."
And when we turn our heads to the right
it means, "Watch out, we're in danger."
We had to be very careful
in the beginning...
...not to mix up "I love you more
than anything in the world"...
...with, "Watch out, we're in danger."
When we raise our left arm it means,
"I want to dance in your arms."
When we make a fist
and put it behind our backs...
...it means, "Let's fuck."
The code grew and grew
as time went by...
...and within a few weeks
we could talk about almost anything...
...without even opening our mouths.
Stop it! That's enough.
Show my parents some respect.
They are playing you music.
- That's okay.
- No, Mother. It is not okay.
Please continue.
Do you want us to perform
the same piece or something else?
Something else.
Didn't her parents play beautifully?
Yes, they did. It was wonderful.
We love each other
and we suit each other.
That's why we've decided
to leave the woods...
...and stay together forever
in the city.
Tomorrow, during the hunt,
we're going to disappear...
...and everyone will think
we've been captured...
...and that we're going to be turned into
dogs or canaries or something.
I think the first thing
I'm going to do...
...when I get into the city
is buy a bathrobe...
...and then we'll go to a pool...
...with a high diving board
perfect for diving.
"And we'll do lots of different things
together, serious things, not silly ones...
...like go for walks in the park
or play the guitar together."
That's where it ends.
There are some notes at the back,
but I don't think they are important.
Read me the notes.
"Portofino: Italian fishing village
and upmarket resort...
...famous for its picturesque harbour.
Population: 439.
Beaches nearby...
...Paraggi Beach, Camogli,
Chiavari and Lavagna.
Serifos: Greek island located
in the western Cyclades."
Where did you find it?
By the river.
Somebody probably dropped it
during the hunt.
Give it to me.
I'll deal with it.
Can you imagine why I brought you
to such a quiet place today?
No.
Because I think it's the perfect spot
for your grave.
Now, cover yourself with soil.
Use your hands.
Over your face too.
You wouldn't want your face
to get eaten by dogs, would you?
If you die before me,
I'll visit you as often as I can.
I promise.
I think we should leave right now.
The three of us coming here
instead of two or four is very dangerous.
Why didn't we think of that earlier?
Highly likely
the doctor will suspect us.
I suggest that we leave
the first chance we get.
Right now, in fact.
Don't be afraid.
No one will suspect a thing.
I bet you weren't expecting
this surprise.
- Isn't it wonderful?
- Yes, it is.
Still, I'd like a few days
just to think it over so that...
...I can maybe have the surgery
when we next come to the city.
What's there to think about?
If it's better to see clearly
or to be shortsighted, is that it?
That's absurd, you know that.
Anyway, this doctor is the best there is
and it's difficult to get an appointment.
I called him months ago
to get him to see you today.
- She's blind.
- Thank you.
Throw down your knife and stand up.
Why did you have to blind me?
You could have blinded him.
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
The drugs are messing
with your head.
If I were you...
...I would try and be a little braver
about the whole thing.
Now, get up and give me your knife
or I'll hit you and take it by force.
- Here I come.
- I swear, I'm going to kill you.
Let go of my hair. You're hurting me.
Just think that when
someone goes blind...
...one of their other senses
is heightened.
You could also catch a dog in the woods
and train it to guide you.
Dogs can do that, you know.
I'll help you catch a dog myself.
Now, calm down
or I'm going to leave you here...
...and I don't think you'll manage
to find meeting point two on your own.
Are you enjoying the view?
Sure.
What happened to your hand?
I was cutting a tree branch with a knife
and I cut myself by accident.
You look handsome today.
Did you get your hair cut?
Thank you.
No, I didn't get a haircut.
I'm going to get my hair cut today.
Look what I brought you.
Oh, thank you so much.
I'm so hungry, I'll eat it right away.
- It's a bigger flashlight.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
It's so big I thought it was a rabbit.
Biggest flashlight I've ever seen.
- Are you ready for tonight?
- Of course I am.
I want to tell you something,
but please don't be angry.
- Okay. What's wrong?
- I can't see anything.
- I'm blind.
- What do you mean?
There's no point in lying to you,
you'll find out sooner or later.
Our leader blinded me in the city.
She must have realised
that I love you and you love me...
...and that we were going
to run away to the city together.
I'm sorry.
You can't see at all?
No, not at all.
And when you asked
if I'd had my hair cut?
I was just saying that...
...so you wouldn't realise
that I can't see.
I'm sorry.
Don't cry.
Crying will make your eyes
hurt more.
We'll find a way.
- What blood type are you?
- B.
Do you like berries? Blueberries?
Blackberries?
No, no.
- Can you play the piano?
- No.
- Plastic cup.
- That's right.
Very good.
Do you speak German?
No.
I could teach you German...
...but it would take a year
to speak the basics, not fluently.
So there's no point.
German is one of the most
difficult languages to learn...
...because its grammar
is very complicated.
I brought you something.
It's a fish.
- Kiwi.
- That's right.
Ten out of 10, again.
Can I give you a kiss?
I can't thank you enough
for the activities and games...
...and for keeping me company,
but you know we can't do that anymore.
Would you like to play another round of
Touch-Guess-Think-Win?
No. That's enough for today.
In any case,
I've run out of things to test you with.
Maybe tomorrow or one of these days.
- Tomorrow morning?
- Well, we'll see.
- Bye.
Good afternoon.
- How are you?
- Fine.
I'm hungry.
You haven't brought me a rabbit
for days.
Or things for me to touch and guess.
I've got good news.
I've had a great idea.
Have you a minute?
What kind of idea?
I raise my left foot.
I bring my elbow to my knee
and tap it twice.
I bring my foot to my knee
and tap it three times.
I lie facedown. I kneel down.
I touch my left cheek
and then lie face up.
Are you sure
you're prepared to do that?
Yes, of course I'm sure.
I wouldn't propose it otherwise.
When?
Tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
We should speed up a little.
I can't go much faster.
These trousers are too tight.
I'm sorry.
It was dark and I couldn't see clearly
and I didn't have time to try them on.
I'm sorry.
Never mind.
There's a bus coming.
It was the hotel coach.
They didn't see us.
Profile.
Fingers.
Elbows.
Would you like me
to show you my belly?
No.
I remember your belly very well.
Smile.
Can I have a knife and fork, please?
Not a butter knife.
- A steak knife.
- Certainly.
Thank you.
I'm going to do it with a knife.
- Do you want me to come with you?
- I'd rather you didn't.
Don't worry.
It's strange at first,
but then you get used to it.
And your other senses
are heightened.
Touch, for example. And hearing.
I know.
I won't be long.
Thank you very much.